yeah yes hi John how are you Dina good
thanks for making the time to talk long
time no see yeah my pleasure
I was there better circumstances yeah
agreed
how was your trip to Greece good
successful I'll tell you I've made what
eight trips to Greece in the last three
years and the the dichotomy between
being in Greece where I'm treated as a
conquering hero and being in the US
where I'm treated as just another ex-con
scumbag is dramatic I go to Greece the
news networks are there to cover my
arrival at the airport the Minister of
Justice sends a car to take me with a
police escort to my hotel and I give
interviews to all the papers and then I
come back here and I'm detained by ice
at the at the airport and it's just a
nightmare
I'm not sure why I'm smiling but that's
funny and sad simultaneously so I guess
I have this mantra that I just repeat at
Dulles Airport you can't stop me from
reentering my own country
I just keep repeating it over and over
and over again
and it's usually between an hour and
four hours later they finally just give
up and stamp my passport let me back in
it's naughty yeah traveling with
Smarties the first piece he has dark
skin it's the first time that I have
ever been like checked and with someone
who's been checked at the airport I yeah
that sucks um but I have a feeling
they're gonna take that as a challenge
now so good luck yeah yeah oh yes
without a doubt yeah so you know it's
always it's always good to get out of
the United States I hate even saying
that because it it might sound wrong to
the wrong people but it's just nice to
be a normal person again and not to be
John Kiriakou who the whistle blower
John Kiriakou who the felon John Barry
Kuryakin the the ex-con you know that
gets tiresome very quickly yeah well I
don't know that I don't think that's how
the people on Facebook see you I think
then you have a lot of admirers people
are good to me it doesn't feel that way
yeah people are good to me on Facebook
they're less Twitter but they're on
Facebook and you know I I was exchanging
messages with someone today I I post
them on Facebook today that I while I
like my current job and it's good fit
for me it's a job it's not a career and
I'm looking for something bigger with
more responsibilities and with more
money and I've gotten a lot of nice
comments but more importantly I got a
lot of private messages and one woman
told me that she was shocked that I
would see myself as as just some
criminal she said after all you've
accomplished after all you've done and
they
you know part of my problem is I have
literally zero remorse for what I did I
know in my heart I did the right thing
and so people want to hear an apology
for violating the law and they're
getting no apology from me the law is
wrong you know it's wrong it's that the
law was wrong and I'm not apologizing
for anything yeah at at Marty's trial
judge Gorton asked him if he wanted to
had anything to say any remorse and he
said I wish I could have done more
sooner there's something to that effect
I yeah I I think that
take ownership like you it seems like
you already do yeah totally that's you
apart
that makes it awesome and people ask me
reporters mostly say so did you do it
well of course I did it yeah now did I
have an intent to break the law no that
wasn't it at all
but it is illegal to classify a crime in
this country and I exposed a crime I
shouldn't have been the one punished for
it yeah should have been punished for it
we're seeing that in Julian Assange's
case publishing you know and with
Manning about exposing crimes and I
think people are getting lost in the
different layers of what the actual you
know is exposing the right thing what
are they exposing I think sometimes
people lose sight of the content and
more of the reaction which seems like
intellectually dishonest yes agreed
yeah it's intellectually dishonest yeah
and you know whenever I sometimes people
disagree with me about something I think
is very black-and-white I say like some
percentage of the world's believes that
the earth is flat and you can't save
everybody but you can't help the people
that are willing to think honestly and
listen to the truth and are open to
facts and not just coming in with
blinders on so you're never gonna be
able to convince everybody but a lot of
people are paying attention that's right
yeah yeah but you know we live in a
society that's that structured in a way
that that there's no
discerning between whistleblowers and
common criminals you know if you've been
to prison your criminal if you've been
convicted of a felony you're a criminal
and that's where the story normally ends
and so you are lumped in with you know
the mortgage fraudsters and the drug
dealers and the pedophiles and it
doesn't matter if you say that you went
to prison for the right reason you know
you went to prison in the in the
interest of transparency people don't
want to hear that they don't want to
hear the details they don't want to get
bogged down in the details either you're
and it's funny that that in our society
in our culture that we've been
conditioned to think that way it's a
shame
you just have to own it harder yeah
that's it you have to come come to the
table with let everybody know right away
I don't yeah I don't see anything to be
ashamed about but I agree it can be very
difficult when
but it can be hard but I I see it as an
asset yep a lot of potential breed yeah
yeah
I wish I remember Marty telling me some
of the stories about how he started his
first jobs or his first job as a senior
systems engineer and he had dropped out
of Drexel was his first semester and he
went to his interview and they said you
know you're good but why should I hire
you versus somebody who has you know
four years of experience already he said
because I and I hope I'm not
paraphrasing but he's like I live eat
and sleep this [__] and if you don't
move out of the way I'll run you over or
something like like he's ready to do the
work and he's there and he's prepared
and the guy was like I couldn't agree
more and he hired him so he's been a
senior systems engineer since eighteen
and you know a lot of people will you
know you'll lose some people but I don't
think those are people that you'd want
to work with anyway yeah that's right
yeah I think you're gonna find the right
fit I sure hope so
yeah um but it's been it's been 85 days
now since I've talked about that you
haven't heard from Marty in nearly three
months are you able to get five days
yeah 85 days almost three months oh
sorry I'm not okay have you heard from
anybody else who's been in touch with
Marty do you have any idea what his
physical condition is like what his
mental condition emotional yeah well he
does have an open case in the Southern
District of New York he's suing the
acting director of the Bureau of P hew
Hurwitz and some of the staff from MCC
nior while he from the time that he did
his hunger strike there
you can read his article at The
Huffington Post called how the Bureau of
Prisons or how the Bo key is trying to
break my hunger strike and he goes into
details and now it's a court case so
we've been able to see some of the
things he's filed he documents a lot of
stuff and includes it's his exhibits and
basically it looks like he's being
punished for helping someone else with
their legal work yeah now this place
this is a CMU communications management
unit which i know that you were at a
modified one yes and you can I'll ask
you more about it but it's basically
like hyper vigilant on your
communications hyper restrictive at this
place it won't even give you a list of
rules there's no handbook to give out so
you can't be you know doing the right
thing or doing the wrong thing because
they can just punish you at any time
yes right point to anything in writing
and so this is insane this is absolutely
insane so they're not letting his mail
go out except for the court and the nut
stuff is filed like 20 days late so but
from his writing we've been able to
gather that most recently one of the
guards did a prea violation against him
Priya's the Prison Rape Elimination Act
he was on the toilet and I guess he was
naked and the guard pulled down a towel
which people use just when you're in the
bathroom because it's in the cell and I
think it was foyer is unlike the guard
stared at him and it's thick like that
really bothers me like and then he in
the filing fee said that there's no
Priya hotlines there's no one you can't
call the prea auditor he can't write to
the DOJ Office of Inspector General
confidentially and he feel and he
suspects reprisal so the content of this
motion that he filed in the Southern
District of New York was saying like I
know you gave me till an extension till
August thirtieth to reply to the
government's motion to dismiss but I
don't know that I can do that not
because I'm not
working on it and trying but because
they're literally preventing me from
work and you know I think there's gonna
be reprisal so you know we're we're able
to gather from the stuff he's filed but
it just is so far from
justice from rules from expectations I
mean my expectations are very different
now than when I started but like this
like this doesn't even resemble America
anymore this is a black site prison that
was created under Bush after 9/11 for
terrorists yes and it's so different
yeah it's so disproportionate to what he
was charged with you know a website
going down for a week to ten years to a
CMU you know I followed Marty's case
closely which you know yeah you've been
great thank you so much oh no no no it's
I wish I could do more it's the least
but Marty's case
in any other courtroom in America even
in the in the horrible Eastern District
of Virginia where so many of us have
gone on trial yeah any other judge would
have given Marty two and a half to three
and a half years and sent him to either
a low security prison or a minimum
security camp maybe possibly to teach
him a lesson they take aways his email
privileges but ten years at Terre Haute
where they have al Qaeda where they have
the Somali pirates who hijacked and
kidnapped captain Phillips where they
have some of the most dangerous
criminals in America and then on top of
that to put him in the CMU which was
created as you rightly noted by george w
bush to house terrorists to keep them
away from the media yeah to prevent them
from passing terrorist instructions out
to their followers that's where Marty
ends up I mean this is overkill of epic
proportions and this just shows this
just shows the the personal animosity
that the that the judge had for Marty
the fix was in from the beginning you
know in retrospect for all the
preparation and all the arguments Marty
never had a chance
not with that judge not with that judge
and not with his court-appointed lawyers
either which are even worse you know at
least at least the prosecution wears
wolf's clothing
you know the defense attorney is
appointed by the court all right you
know put on sheep's clothing on top
which is just I don't know how they
found a way to be more offensive than
the prosecution but they found it yeah
the bad part too is that if you appeal
to the Court of Appeals they won't
rehear facts of the case they won't rule
on whether or not something is fair
they'll rule only on the application of
law so they won't say oh boy this guy
got screwed
he should be resentenced or this guy got
screwed he should go back to have
another trial they don't do that kind of
thing
they'll rule only on the
constitutionality of the decisions that
the prosecution made and that the judge
made and overturning a district court
verdict is almost unheard of anywhere
well you know at the time we did Marty
did file something with the Court of
Appeals I think it was about the judges
conflict of interest yes
they didn't rule in time and they didn't
do whatever but in this case I do think
we have a strong case no the Court of
Appeals will agree as remains to be seen
but we do have some strong issues and
you know with the Court of Appeals -
there are so many appeals thousands and
thousands of Appeals most of which are
pro se they come from the prisoners
themselves that preliminary decisions
are made by panels of three three of the
nine appeals court judge judges and
usually they're not really even made by
those three they're made by the clerk's
clerking for those three and so if you
don't get satisfaction in your first
pass at the circuit court of appeals you
have the right to ask for and on what's
called an unboxing
en ba NC hearing and that means a panel
of all nine judges has to hear your
appeal now your appeal has to have a
constitutional basis marquise I think is
rife with constitutional basis and some
justice now one good thing you're in the
Marty's in the what the First Circuit
yes yes Boston yes yeah the First
Circuit has a reputation as being
relatively liberal unlike the Fourth
Circuit which is in Richmond Virginia
seven of the nine judges were
pointed by the two bushes and so nobody
ever wins in the Fourth Circuit the
First Circuit's different you might get
some satisfaction there and even if you
even if you lose at the circuit court
level because you have constitutional
issues raised in this case you can then
appeal to the Supreme Court and because
Marty didn't take a plea because he went
to trial he automatically has standing
so you still have a ways to go you have
three different stops on the road to
exoneration that you you need to exhaust
I think he's actually not in bad shape
right now
but in a table but yeah well you know I
think that this is actually a pretty
good case for president Trump I think
you have a conservative girl she doesn't
need to be conservative but it does
happen
that it happened to a conservative
family who was separated from her family
forced in a psych ward by the state by
liberal Massachusetts where they tried
to you know get her adopted out into
foster care and then another family and
it's just government intrusion into the
family unit and when the DOJ and the
government became aware of this
like we said similar to your case
they're not are similar to
whistleblowers they're not interested in
writing the problem keeping families
with their parents and you know away
from lack of investigations rulings that
aren't based on facts or evidence and
instead they want to protect Harvard
it's a harvard institution they're
interested in money and this is just a
huge case of DOJ malfeasance going after
the wrong person and in some ways I
think that Trump has been really great
about being able to separate himself
from the government and do what's right
for individuals I know that people have
split feelings on him and I'm not trying
to deny anyone's feelings but I think
this is a fun if I think that's
something that I really like about him
is that he's so different than everyone
that came before him and it's it feels
like a ray of hope for a lot of people
that have been so ignored by Obama which
I know that you agree with yeah and I
think you know just him continuing to
pardon and commute sentences it's a
really good way to stick it to the DOJ
that they can cause havoc on people's
life but Trump is the final check and I
think I think this is a good case for
him I think you are exactly right I am
NOT a natural Donald Trump supporter but
with that said Donald Trump has done
something that very few presidents have
done in this area
Benni yeah sorry and it means it's a
good we're really the last one that
hardened people whenever he felt that he
had founded injustice the last one to do
that was Abraham Lincoln Abraham Lincoln
pardoned people all through his
administration I always liked that guy
I always liked him yeah we presidents
don't have the guts to do that though
wait until a lame-duck period after an
election and before a following
inauguration to issue pardons this
president hasn't done that and he's he's
partly some very controversial figures
like Joe Arpaio the former sheriff of
Maricopa County Arizona
dinesh d'souza the conservative
publisher and activist this Navy guy who
who was convicted of of taking
photographs on a submarine that's okay
Scooter Libby who was who never should
have been convicted of the ridiculous
crimes that he was convicted of perjury
and making false statements so this
president's not afraid to stick his
beacon where where a right or wrong
needs to be righted and I'll tell you
another thing
Jared Kushner for all of his from of his
detractors and and his problems he's
right on this issue of of judicial
reform and sentencing reform and he's
personally intervened to get a lot of
people out of prison in fact the
president famously commuted the sentence
of a woman who was doing life without
parole for selling drugs African
American woman this is one of the
highest profile commutations that
president Trump had done I learned just
yesterday from a friend of mine who
happens to work in the White House yeah
the Jared Kushner actually called the
CEO of Walmart to get this woman a job
haha called
every six months since to make sure
she's doing okay Wow so there Alice
Cooper right yeah that's right yes yeah
you know you know where Jared's uh share
its passion
comes from yes father did 14 father from
I'm security federal prison what's
what's that guy what's his name the old
governor of New Jersey who put his
father away I'm for Chris Christie chris
Christie yeah that's why could I think
that's why Chris Christie never got a
job in the White House
that's exactly why Chris can't come on
the yep you pick the wrong side yeah and
I think that I often feel that I wish
judges and lawyers and people who are
going who are making decisions in the
criminal justice system had to actually
experience what it's like before they're
in a position to make decisions on
somebody else's behalf just because like
you know having gone through this stuff
and sing it myself
firsthand and I've seen only only a 30th
of what Marty Fein and I've only heard
but there are so many cases of FBI
entrapment bogus charges of just and not
only that but like they bring charges
only to drop them later after years of
having somebody spent wrongfully in
jails like the older people
that's called stacking it's called what
charge stacking they charge you with
multiple multiple felonies they wait
until you go bankrupt and then they
offer to drop all the charges but one if
you take a plea that's why the
government according to ProPublica wins
ninety eight point two percent of their
cases let me tell you a story about yes
the FBI from from 2009 to middle of 2011
I was the chief investigator on the
Senate Foreign Relations Committee Wow
yeah I was working for John Kerry at the
time and that it was an important
position I was one of four senior staff
members and so one of the great things
about that job about any job working on
the Foreign Relations committees you get
to have lunch with foreign diplomats all
the time and you talk about the issues
of the day what's going on in the world
Foreign Affairs
one day
the number three at the Japanese embassy
called me and invited me to lunch and so
we went to lunch in a little place on
Capitol Hill delightful lunch I remember
it I remember what we talked about we
talked about Israeli elections and
Turkish elections and the Middle East
peace process and at the end of the
lunch
he asked me so what's what's next for
you
I said actually I think I'm gonna resign
soon I promise Senator Kerry I'd give
him two years it's been two and a half I
have five kids I need to really start
making some money to put them through
college and very excitedly he said you
know in a very loud whisper no if you
give me money I'm sorry if you give me
information I can give you money
and I said shame on you you have any
idea how many times I've made that pitch
what's the matter with you and I got up
I walked out and I walked directly
without stopping to the office of the
Senate security officer and I went in
and I said I was just pitched by foreign
intelligence officer so he asked me the
details he told me to write the story on
a standalone computer not connected to
the internet so it couldn't be
intercepted he printed out the memo that
I wrote and he hand carried it to the
FBI the next day he told me that two FBI
agents would be up to interview me so
sure enough a day later two FBI agents
came I repeated the entire story and
they said okay here's what we want you
to do we want you to call him back
invite him to lunch and try and get him
to tell you exactly what information he
wants and how much he's willing to pay
for it and because I'm a patriot I said
you want me to wear a wire or something
and they said no we'll be at the next
table we're gonna listen to the whole
conversation I said great I called the
guy I invited him to lunch he accepted
the morning that I was supposed to have
lunch with him the FBI called me back
and said that something had come up they
couldn't be there but to go ahead and do
the lunch and just write him another
memo so I did
and then they asked me to do it a third
time and a fourth time and a fifth time
and in the final lunch the guy gave me a
little gift of chopsticks and he told me
that he had been promoted and he was
being transferred he was going to be the
number two at the Japanese Embassy in
Cairo I shook his hand
I wished him good luck and I never saw
him again
a year later I've been arrested and we
get fifteen thousand pages of discovery
from the Justice Department and as it
turns out there never was any Japanese
diplomat he was an FBI agent undercover
trying to get me to commit real
espionage because they wanted to charge
me with espionage but I hadn't committed
espionage and finally their supervisor
who's now infamous in his own right by
the name of Peter Strock said we should
just drop this case because I dropped
this operation because the guy's
obviously not going to take the bait
I kept reporting the contact back to the
FBI what they wanted me to do was to
report maybe some of the contact and
then take some money whisper little
information and then they could grab me
but I was writing a blow-by-blow of
every topic and every issue in these
meetings and finally they just had to
give up and in the end I was charged
with three counts of espionage all of
which were dropped because I hadn't
committed espionage as hard as they
tried they could not get me to commit
espionage well everyone knows Peters
drug is the pillar of the community
yeah integrity oh yeah cheating on his
wife with a woman who's cheating on her
husband and all the while texting each
other and plotting how to take down the
newly elected president of the United
States got it yeah damn
that's crazy they'll stop at nothing and
remember and this is kind of pedestrian
but it's important this is how these
people get promoted they're just going
functionaries they're just going with
your notches in their belt for the next
career level for sure that's it
that's no one you know one of the things
that I talked about the Marty and I
talked about before he was arrested was
TV shows propaganda on TV that make the
FBI and the government in the courtroom
look like a place that doesn't resemble
real life at all you identify with the
prosecutors with the judge with the FBI
and it is just so different in real life
they do not show the tactics and so to
some extent we stopped watching shows
like that because it's propagated death
I stopped watching live which was my
favorite show in the world
John me to turn on Sam Waterston and I
was like you unethical bastard how dare
you or just when you know that that guy
hasn't done anything wrong I couldn't
watch it anymore it hurt yeah it hurts
some shows are better than others but
yeah I know it's hard you know and I I
think you and I both kind of share a
libertarian streak like my life you live
your life but you know when it really
came down to it when I was in the
courtroom during Marty's trial be the
ultimate deciders are a jury of your
peers and that really struck a struck
something in me about what it means to
be libertarian and what it means to not
just worry about myself but you know I
feel like we have a responsibility to
it's too late for us like for you and I
but there's a lot of people that if they
hear about what's happened to Marty into
you can make decisions before things
happen to them and like it's important
for our peers to know that I I hate that
the gut I hate that the jury knew so
little about judge Gordon and about the
prosecutors and the dirty tactics they
go to and how they judge Gorton won't
even let Marty youself the defense of
another about Justyna like he didn't
even let that be a defense and the jury
didn't find out about that but you know
there was a lady on Marie's jury um she
now judge Gorton was Aaron Swartz's
judged to know Aaron Swartz was an
internet pioneer he helped co-found read
it he was very active against SOPA and
PIPA and she said during trial she asked
to be removed from from the case she
said you know it's come to my attention
and we didn't do anything it's just like
she's just that it came to my attention
I remember Aaron Swartz I don't want to
be part of this I don't want Marty to go
to jail there's some something to that
extent it's actually on the court
transcript I believe and judge Gordon's
like do you think you can follow the
rules and she said yes they ended up
convicting Marty and then acts at the
conviction at this and she she mouthed
to him I'm sorry and he now back it's
okay and it was just heartbreaking yeah
it's just
I'm like I want I want to talk about
good things I want to talk about good
things I don't want to talk about all
this terribleness that's going on I want
our justice system to be a beacon of
light goodness and hope and light the
way that people used to think about
America it's not it doesn't resemble it
I seen speeches all the time when I was
at the CIA working on on Iraq I was at
the CIA for 15 years yeah you know
Saddam Hussein would run for re-election
every three or four years and he would
get 98% we would laugh and laugh you
know about what a joke it was and the
fix was in and then the Justice
Department wins 98 percent of its cases
and we say they're geniuses my god
they're geniuses they won 98 percent
their case and that's the fix in there
too
you know what am i one of my attorneys
yelled at me one day we received what
was called by the Justice Department
their best and final offer to Ripley
my wife and I my ex-wife and I stayed up
all night talking about this little all
night and around 6 a.m. I emailed my
attorneys and I said I decided to turn
it down that once I get in front of a
jury they're gonna realize how
ridiculous this is
yeah and the attorneys drove to my house
by seven o'clock in the morning they
were there I put on a pot of coffee and
the the lawyer that I liked and
respected the most I had 11 attorneys
right so the one that I liked and
respected the most the head of the
white-collar defense practice at the 4th
largest law firm in the world
bacon Gump and Strauss pulled me aside
and said you know what your problem is
your problem is you think this is about
justice and it's not about justice it's
about mitigating damage take the deal
and he was right in retrospect looking
back I never had a prayer I never had a
chance of acquittal even though I knew
in my heart I had not done anything
wrong but I never had a chance because
the system is structured so that you
don't have a chance that's why almost
every one of those 98.2%
of the cases that the Justice Department
hey they win through plea deals because
you don't have a chance
almost nobody goes to trial and those
who do lose
unless your name is John Edwards
remember John Edwards he was the vice
presidential nominee for the Democrats
in 2004 I don't think I was born yet
just getting OH
bunch of federal felonies and he said oh
no you don't and he went to trial but
the guy's worth 40 million dollars and
he spent eight million of his own money
on his defense yeah he was acquitted
which you could do that's the Eastern
District of North Carolina when you have
unlimited resources yeah which is what
the government comes at you with yes
exactly yeah no it's insane
I just I just feel like it's it's urgent
that it's untenable for Marty to stay at
that CMU it is so frustrating to not be
able to speak to him to know that he's
in such bad conditions like he's strong
and a fighter but this is insane it
makes me so angry they can break it
buddy this is the sad thing about his
situation I actually served time with a
guy an Iraqi Kurd who had come to us I
was at Loreto FCI Loretto Pennsylvania
he had come to us from the CMU in Terre
Haute and he was in the modified CMU
with me at Loreto and and he I mean he
had a story as sad as Marty's this guy
prison was the last place this guy
belong but the deck was stacked against
him and they put him to CMU because he
was an Arab or he wasn't really an Arab
he was occurred but you get the idea
yeah and so I asked him how did you get
out of Terre Haute I did anybody got out
of Terre Haute and he said it took me a
little while to to learn the ropes but
the only way to get out is to keep your
mouth shut for years and after four
years they decided okay well this guy
hasn't caused us any problems in four
years will downgrade him to a low and
we'll send him out and that's what they
did and the guy had already been in
prison he started in a maximum-security
penitentiary had already been in prison
for 12
years yeah but four years in that CMU
and they finally decided just downgrade
him you must have kept his mouth really
quiet because they can make up charges
for anything and they do they don't
that's like being a prison lawyer or
whatever it's called jailhouse lawyer is
that's that's not a crime that's not a
bad thing that happens in every jail in
America there's something else illegal
work so when I was at Loreto they caught
a couple of guys acting as jailhouse
lawyers nine times out of ten they'll
either turn the other way or just say
hey you know you really shouldn't be
doing that
all the times I saw guys working on
other guys cases at Loreto twice they
wrote up a shot disciplinary violation
they call them shots and and the guys
went to solitary for you know two weeks
three weeks and that was it and then
they tell you hey you don't do that
again and then it's all over but three
months now incommunicado that's over the
top
and Counting there's no ending yeah we
don't know what it's gonna be six months
well and he's a journalist too like
they're stopping his First Amendment
right from publishing about articles and
communicating with other journalists and
it's just so wrong on so many levels
that's why I feel like well you know
that's really important for Trump to
intervene on this case that's an
important point you raise they try to
stop me from communicating with other
journalists I said you can't do that I
have a First Amendment right they said
oh no you don't I said oh yes actually I
do
it's in VOP regulations
so in law library and I printed the
bo-peep regulations and I have actually
laid it out right there in the mailroom
and I had you cannot stop me from
communicating with journalists and then
two of them were sort of arguing well
this this is old I said no this was
published a month ago yeah it's brand
spankin new and then whatever them
looked at means that just just go we'll
send it just go and they sent it they
don't even know their own regulations
and they know that you are at such an
incredible disadvantage that they can do
almost anything they want to you and you
have no recourse I know that's why you
got to keep up the pressure from the
outside because he can't do it himself
in there his hands are tied
yeah it's been and I hope journalists
understand and take that seriously into
heart what a big role they play in
working with imprisoned journalists and
it's how important they are and I hope
that they take it seriously because they
really matter and Dana he's not allowed
to have visitors either is he definitely
Wally's not incommunicado and even if he
could you know post trial they usually
allow for what's a call to in-person
visits yes where you can see them and
touch them but not at the CMU it's
through glass there's no opportunity to
ever spend
time with a loved one besides birth
through glass and we haven't been doing
that since he's been in jail and you
know pretrial for the most part except
for once when he was in Florida because
and he said this night I kind of agree
but it's just really demoralizing to see
your loved ones that way you know what I
mean
it is yeah and so we haven't done that
we just you know talk on the phone and
stuff and now I can't even do that 80 80
I think it's 85 days now cuz the last
time I spoke to him was April 26th it's
just like absolutely insane just
terrible
yeah so by us it's good to see you it's
always a pleasure to see ya Austin any
time I don't know it's possible you know
my sister lives up there she lives in
Bedford New Hampshire so yeah when I
when I go visit I always take the kids
to Boston we go yeah good alright um
thank you so much for talking thank you
as a pleasure
yeah very best of luck to both you and
Marty thanks and we should you to say on
some Penn I look forward to it
okay thanks take care bye John bye bye